

Dzmitry Karatayeu









Front-End Developer

Profile

I'm 25 years old Front-End developer based in Minsk with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, Typescript, HTML, CSS, JS. Currently, I am improving my skills with a view to expand them with new technologies.

Also, I'm planning to study Node.js because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer.

Contacts



+375 29 871 28 86





Minsk, Belarus

Skill Highlights

- React/Redux
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/REST api/Postman
- TDD/Jest/Storybook
- React-hook-form/Formik
- MaterialUI/Ant Design
- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Git

Languages

English – Intermediate Russian - Native

Work Experience

Web Developer

Aug 2021 - Present

Freelance | Minsk, Belarus

- React development using redux, react-redux, react-routerdom, redux-thunk, axios, formik, ant-design libraries.
- Work with Hooks, TypeScript
- Refactoring, bug fixing, registration and login form creation
- Reusable components development

Acting System Administrator & Boiler building master

Sep 2019 - Aug 2021

Housing and utilities | Logoisk, Belarus

- Performed two jobs at the same time
- Control the operations of the facility
- Updating the 1C system, maintaining the software
- IT support officer for the personnel

Education

IT-INCUBATOR, Front-End | Minsk, Belarus

2022

 Front-end developer with teamwork experience in creating applications by using React, Redux, TypeScript, Axios and other technologies

Polotsk State University | Polotsk, Belarus

2014 - 2019

Faculty of Heat, Water, Air and Gas Supply, Civil engineer

Polotsk State University | Polotsk, Belarus

2017 - 2019

Faculty of Finance and Economics, Production manager